export const quizzes = [
  {
    id: '4d631310-39e0-4cc5-bcd4-638f4f1650e3',
    title: 'Spanish Vocabulary Challenge: Test Your Knowledge!',
    description:
      "Are you ready to put your Spanish skills to the test? This intermediate-level quiz will challenge your vocabulary knowledge with a mix of serious and amusing questions. Let's see how well you know your Spanish words!",
    difficulty: 'intermediate',
    language: 'Spanish',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'manzana',
        options: ['manzana', 'pera', 'naranja', 'uvas'],
        question: "What is the Spanish word for 'apple'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'estudiar',
        options: ['escribir', 'comer', 'estudiar', 'correr'],
        question: "Which verb means 'to study' in Spanish?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'gato',
        options: ['perro', 'gato', 'pájaro', 'pez'],
        question: "What is the Spanish word for 'cat'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'baño',
        options: ['cocina', 'dormitorio', 'baño', 'sala'],
        question: 'Where would you go if you needed to use the bathroom?',
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Un elefante se balanceaba sobre la tela de una araña.',
        question: "Translate this to Spanish: 'An elephant was balancing on a spider's web.'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '77053034-6ede-4bd3-a6e6-a024c9ef5715',
    title: "Beginner's Fun Spanish Vocabulary Quiz!",
    description:
      "Dive into the basics of Spanish with this fun and engaging quiz! Perfect for beginners, these questions range from the practical to the silly, making learning enjoyable. Let's see how much Spanish you know!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'Spanish',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'hola',
        options: ['hola', 'adiós', 'gracias', 'por favor'],
        question: "What is the Spanish word for 'hello'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'gracias',
        options: ['sí', 'no', 'gracias', 'por favor'],
        question: "How do you say 'thank you' in Spanish?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'azul',
        options: ['rojo', 'verde', 'azul', 'amarillo'],
        question: "What is the Spanish word for 'blue'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'perro',
        options: ['gato', 'perro', 'ratón', 'pájaro'],
        question: "What is the Spanish word for 'dog'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Tengo un pato en mi sombrero.',
        question: "Translate this to Spanish: 'I have a duck in my hat.'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        id: '3d299e8d-a70d-4da9-bb48-c32928139d01',
        title: 'Kickstart Your Spanish: Fun Vocabulary Quiz!',
        description:
          "Jump into the world of Spanish with this engaging beginner-level quiz! Featuring a mix of practical and whimsical questions, this quiz will help you learn and have fun at the same time. Let's get started!",
        difficulty: 'beginner',
        language: 'Spanish',
        questions: [
          {
            correct_answer: 'hola',
            options: ['hola', 'adiós', 'gracias', 'por favor'],
            question: "What is the Spanish word for 'hello'?",
            type: 'single_choice',
          },
          {
            correct_answer: 'rojo',
            options: ['azul', 'verde', 'rojo', 'negro'],
            question: "What is the Spanish word for 'red'?",
            type: 'single_choice',
          },
          {
            correct_answer: 'escuela',
            options: ['casa', 'escuela', 'tienda', 'parque'],
            question: "What is the Spanish word for 'school'?",
            type: 'single_choice',
          },
          {
            correct_answer: 'plátano',
            options: ['manzana', 'naranja', 'plátano', 'pera'],
            question: "Which word means 'banana' in Spanish?",
            type: 'single_choice',
          },
          {
            correct_answer: 'Tengo un elefante en mi habitación.',
            question: "Translate this to Spanish: 'I have an elephant in my room.'",
            type: 'free_text',
          },
        ],
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '96240b80-faa0-4cdd-b81d-4e7f34cf3362',
    title: 'Master Your Spanish: Advanced Vocabulary Challenge!',
    description:
      "Ready to take your Spanish skills to the next level? This advanced-level quiz will put your vocabulary knowledge to the test with a mix of challenging and unconventional questions. Whether you're a language enthusiast or a seasoned learner, this quiz will push your limits!",
    difficulty: 'advanced',
    language: 'Spanish',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'anticonstitucionalmente',
        options: [
          'desafortunadamente',
          'anticonstitucionalmente',
          'increíblemente',
          'responsablemente',
        ],
        question: "Which Spanish word is the longest and means 'unconstitutionally'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'espectrofotometría',
        options: ['escritura', 'espectrofotometría', 'espacio', 'especialización'],
        question: "Which word refers to the measurement of spectra and means 'spectrophotometry'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia',
        options: [
          'hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia',
          'onomatopoeia',
          'antidisestablishmentarianism',
          'supercalifragilisticexpialidocious',
        ],
        question: 'What is the fear of long words called in Spanish?',
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: "¿Cuántas letras tiene la palabra 'murciélago'?",
        question: "How many letters does the word 'murciélago' have? (Answer in Spanish)",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'La lluvia en Sevilla es una maravilla.',
        question: "Translate this Spanish tongue twister: 'La lluvia en Sevilla es una maravilla.'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'ac02020f-2411-4275-9591-c565123828a9',
    title: "Spanish Vocabulary Adventure: Beginner's Quest!",
    description:
      "Embark on an exciting journey into Spanish vocabulary with this beginner's quiz! From everyday words to quirky phrases, this quiz offers a fun way to start learning Spanish. Get ready for an adventure!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'Spanish',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'hola',
        options: ['hola', 'adiós', 'gracias', 'sí'],
        question: "What is the Spanish word for 'hello'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'rojo',
        options: ['rojo', 'azul', 'verde', 'amarillo'],
        question: "What color is 'red' in Spanish?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'amigo',
        options: ['amigo', 'perro', 'gato', 'casa'],
        question: "What does 'amigo' mean in English?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: '¿Cómo estás?',
        question: "How do you say 'How are you?' in Spanish?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Tengo un tigre en mi bañera.',
        question: "Translate this to Spanish: 'I have a tiger in my bathtub.'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'ff30cc22-f968-4ba2-815b-33192900cb35',
    title: "German Vocabulary Adventure: Beginner's Quest!",
    description:
      "Embark on an exciting journey into German vocabulary with this beginner's quiz! From everyday words to quirky phrases, this quiz offers a fun way to start learning German. Get ready for an adventure!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'German',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'Hallo',
        options: ['Hallo', 'Auf Wiedersehen', 'Danke', 'Bitte'],
        question: "What is the German word for 'hello'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'rot',
        options: ['rot', 'blau', 'grün', 'gelb'],
        question: "What color is 'red' in German?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Freund',
        options: ['Freund', 'Hund', 'Katze', 'Haus'],
        question: "What does 'Freund' mean in English?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Wie geht es dir?',
        question: "How do you say 'How are you?' in German?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Ich habe einen Tiger in meiner Badewanne.',
        question: "Translate this to German: 'I have a tiger in my bathtub.'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'd23207af-4bf4-4de5-a2bf-0e4d1311f8c9',
    title: 'German Vocabulary Challenge: Elevate Your Skills!',
    description:
      'Take your German vocabulary to the next level with this intermediate-level quiz! From practical words to intriguing phrases, this quiz will test and expand your knowledge in a fun and engaging way. Get ready for a challenge!',
    difficulty: 'intermediate',
    language: 'German',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'Guten Tag',
        options: ['Guten Tag', 'Auf Wiedersehen', 'Danke', 'Bitte'],
        question: "What is the German equivalent of 'Good day'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'blau',
        options: ['rot', 'blau', 'grün', 'gelb'],
        question: "What color is 'blue' in German?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Schwester',
        options: ['Bruder', 'Schwester', 'Hund', 'Katze'],
        question: "What does 'Schwester' mean in English?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Wie heißt du?',
        question: "How do you ask 'What is your name?' in German?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Ich habe einen Elefanten im Kühlschrank.',
        question: "Translate this to German: 'I have an elephant in my refrigerator.'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '71c7edc9-99e4-4667-a653-9a0441758aa7',
    title: 'German Vocabulary Mastery: Advanced Challenge!',
    description:
      'Ready to push the boundaries of your German vocabulary? This advanced-level quiz will challenge even the most seasoned learners with a mix of intricate words and bizarre phrases. Embrace the challenge and elevate your German skills to new heights!',
    difficulty: 'advanced',
    language: 'German',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer:
          'Donaudampfschifffahrtselektrizitätenhauptbetriebswerkbauunterbeamtengesellschaft',
        options: [
          'Eichhörnchen',
          'Donaudampfschifffahrtselektrizitätenhauptbetriebswerkbauunterbeamtengesellschaft',
          'Rechtschreibung',
          'Weihnachtsbaum',
        ],
        question:
          "What is the longest German word that means 'association for subordinate officials of the head office management of the Danube steamboat electrical services'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Backpfeifengesicht',
        options: ['Finger', 'Hand', 'Backpfeifengesicht', 'Fuß'],
        question: "Which German word means 'a face badly in need of a fist'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Oachkatzlschwoaf',
        options: ['Eichhörnchen', 'Oachkatzlschwoaf', 'Eichel', 'Baum'],
        question: "Which Bavarian word means 'squirrel's tail'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Waschmaschine',
        question: "How do you say 'washing machine' in German?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Der Elefant trinkt Wasser mit einem Strohhalm.',
        question: "Translate this to German: 'The elephant drinks water with a straw.'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'ba47b475-6036-4db1-be96-4bed61fb1dc7',
    title: "German Vocabulary Adventure: Beginner's Quest!",
    description:
      "Embark on an exciting journey into German vocabulary with this beginner's quiz! From everyday words to quirky phrases, this quiz offers a fun way to start learning German. Get ready for an adventure!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'German',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'Hallo',
        options: ['Hallo', 'Auf Wiedersehen', 'Danke', 'Bitte'],
        question: "What is the German word for 'hello'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'rot',
        options: ['rot', 'blau', 'grün', 'gelb'],
        question: "What color is 'red' in German?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Freund',
        options: ['Freund', 'Hund', 'Katze', 'Haus'],
        question: "What does 'Freund' mean in English?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Wie geht es dir?',
        question: "How do you say 'How are you?' in German?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Ich habe einen Tiger in meiner Badewanne.',
        question: "Translate this to German: 'I have a tiger in my bathtub.'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'f5ca7ab7-5f4e-4253-823f-8304d92cbdb8',
    title: 'Dive into Esperanto: Fun and Engaging Vocabulary Quiz!',
    description:
      'Welcome to the Esperanto Vocabulary Quiz! This quiz is designed to test your basic knowledge of Esperanto words, ranging from everyday vocabulary to some playful and absurd terms. Perfect for beginners, this quiz will help you get acquainted with one of the most intriguing constructed languages. Have fun and learn something new!',
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'Esperanto',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'hundo',
        options: ['kato', 'hundo', 'birdo', 'fiŝo'],
        question: "What is the Esperanto word for 'dog'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'bona',
        options: ['bona', 'malbona', 'rapida', 'nova'],
        question: "Which of these words means 'good' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'afero',
        options: ['afero', 'libro', 'domo', 'suno'],
        question: "What is the Esperanto word for 'thing'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'ĉu vi parolas Esperanton?',
        question: "How do you ask 'Do you speak Esperanto?' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'ŝafo',
        options: ['ŝafo', 'elefanto', 'tigro', 'ĉevalo'],
        question: "Which of these animals is called 'ŝafo' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '0ee918be-7d33-41e8-a400-168eb5ac7fd9',
    title: 'Esperanto Exploration: Intermediate Vocabulary Challenge',
    description:
      "Ready to put your Esperanto skills to the test? This quiz is perfect for those who have moved beyond the basics and want to dive deeper into this fascinating language. From everyday words to some quirky and unexpected terms, this quiz will challenge and entertain you. Let's see how well you know Esperanto!",
    difficulty: 'intermediate',
    language: 'Esperanto',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'flugilo',
        options: ['flugilo', 'mano', 'kruro', 'kapo'],
        question: "What is the Esperanto word for 'wing'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'viando',
        options: ['viando', 'frukto', 'legomo', 'trinkaĵo'],
        question: "Which of these words means 'meat' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'interesa',
        options: ['interesa', 'peza', 'rapida', 'malgranda'],
        question: "Which of these words means 'interesting' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Mi ŝatas manĝi ĉokoladon.',
        question: "How do you say 'I like to eat chocolate.' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'krokodilo',
        options: ['krokodilo', 'elefanto', 'hipopotamo', 'leono'],
        question: "Which of these animals is called 'krokodilo' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '0fca85f3-2e80-46b8-9bfc-b1f6e39caa58',
    title: 'Mastering Esperanto: Advanced Vocabulary Quiz',
    description:
      "Think you've mastered Esperanto? This advanced quiz will put your skills to the ultimate test. From complex words to some that are downright whimsical, this quiz will challenge even the most experienced Esperanto speakers. Are you ready to prove your proficiency?",
    difficulty: 'advanced',
    language: 'Esperanto',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'malfacila',
        options: ['malfacila', 'facila', 'komenca', 'rapida'],
        question: "Which of these words means 'difficult' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'vortaro',
        options: ['libro', 'vortaro', 'gazeto', 'artikolo'],
        question: "What is the Esperanto word for 'dictionary'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'ŝercema',
        options: ['serioza', 'ŝercema', 'enigma', 'nervoza'],
        question: "Which word means 'humorous' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Mi amas la lingvon Esperanton!',
        question: "How do you say 'I love the Esperanto language!' in Esperanto?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'eksplodas',
        options: ['eksplodas', 'brulas', 'krias', 'kuracas'],
        question: "What is the Esperanto word for 'explode'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'a04024ff-d497-4307-abdd-6ad8f83649a2',
    title: "Embark on Estonian Adventure: Beginner's Vocabulary Quest!",
    description:
      "Welcome to the Estonian Vocabulary Quiz! Whether you're just starting to explore this beautiful language or looking to refresh your basic knowledge, this quiz is perfect for you. From everyday words to some fun and quirky terms, let's dive into Estonian together!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'Estonian',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'koer',
        options: ['kass', 'koer', 'lind', 'kala'],
        question: "What is the Estonian word for 'dog'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'hea',
        options: ['hea', 'halb', 'kiire', 'uus'],
        question: "Which of these words means 'good' in Estonian?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'asi',
        options: ['asi', 'raamat', 'maja', 'päike'],
        question: "What is the Estonian word for 'thing'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Kas sa räägid eesti keelt?',
        question: "How do you ask 'Do you speak Estonian?' in Estonian?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'hunt',
        options: ['hunt', 'elevant', 'tiiger', 'hobune'],
        question: "Which of these animals is called 'hunt' in Estonian?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'eba0c94e-ef24-4f06-bc73-838bd3153152',
    title: 'Estonian Odyssey: Intermediate Vocabulary Voyage!',
    description:
      "Embark on an Estonian Odyssey with this intermediate level vocabulary quiz! Whether you're brushing up on your Estonian skills or taking the next step in your language journey, this quiz will take you on a linguistic voyage through everyday words and some unexpected gems. Let's explore Estonian together!",
    difficulty: 'intermediate',
    language: 'Estonian',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'lendama',
        options: ['jooksma', 'hüppama', 'sõitma', 'lendama'],
        question: "Which of these words means 'to fly' in Estonian?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'nälg',
        options: ['uni', 'nälg', 'janu', 'külm'],
        question: "What is the Estonian word for 'hunger'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'õnnelik',
        options: ['õnnelik', 'kurb', 'vihane', 'ärritunud'],
        question: "Which word means 'happy' in Estonian?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'Kui vana sa oled?',
        question: "How do you ask 'How old are you?' in Estonian?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'jänes',
        options: ['jänes', 'karu', 'hunt', 'rebane'],
        question: "Which of these animals is called 'jänes' in Estonian?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '9a90e145-8b45-412b-8bb6-d1eb0505caed',
    title: 'Estonian Enigma: Advanced Vocabulary Challenge!',
    description:
      'Welcome to the Estonian Enigma, an advanced vocabulary challenge designed to push your Estonian skills to the limit! This quiz will test your knowledge of both common and obscure Estonian words, from serious to downright absurd. Are you ready to unlock the secrets of the Estonian language?',
    difficulty: 'advanced',
    language: 'Estonian',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'ümberpööramatu',
        options: ['pööratav', 'pöördumatu', 'mõistetav', 'ümberpööramatu'],
        question: "Which of these words means 'irreversible' in Estonian?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'laanes',
        options: ['kirde', 'edela', 'kagu', 'laanes'],
        question: "What is the Estonian word for 'west'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'nähtamatu roosa elevandikaravan',
        question: "Translate the following phrase into English: 'nähtamatu roosa elevandikaravan'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'vahtraleht',
        options: ['tammepuu leht', 'kuuseokas', 'vahtraleht', 'kadakamarja oks'],
        question: "Which of these means 'maple leaf' in Estonian?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'tuulepealne',
        options: ['tuulepealne', 'päikese poolne', 'varjuline', 'külm'],
        question: "Which word means 'windward' in Estonian?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '24819e90-15a8-4742-b7ed-8eb814d17b25',
    title: "Journey into Huttese: Beginner's Vocabulary Expedition!",
    description:
      "Welcome to the Journey into Huttese! This quiz is your gateway to the fascinating language spoken by the Hutts. Whether you're a newcomer or a seasoned traveler in the Star Wars universe, this beginner's vocabulary expedition will introduce you to some essential words and phrases in Huttese. Let's embark on this adventure together!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'Huttese',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'pateesa',
        options: ['jabba', 'jedi', 'pateesa', 'sith'],
        question: "What does 'pateesa' mean in Huttese?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'boonta',
        options: ['sleemo', 'boonta', 'meeska', 'konya'],
        question: "Translate 'boonta' into Basic (Galactic Basic Standard).",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'shag',
        options: ['crumb', 'shag', 'slimy', 'koocho'],
        question: "What does 'shag' mean in Huttese?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'jaja',
        options: ['no', 'yes', 'maybe', 'jaja'],
        question: "Which word means 'yes' in Huttese?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'moochalaka',
        question: "Translate 'moochalaka' into Basic (Galactic Basic Standard).",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '0883b777-dc3c-4b70-9614-670a4132dd8a',
    title: 'Unravel the Secrets of Huttese: Intermediate Vocabulary Quest!',
    description:
      'Get ready to unravel the secrets of Huttese in this intermediate vocabulary quest! From everyday phrases to some of the more obscure terms, this quiz will test your knowledge of the language spoken by the notorious Hutts. Are you up for the challenge?',
    difficulty: 'intermediate',
    language: 'Huttese',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'patawan',
        options: ['patawan', 'pateeke', 'patuna', 'patila'],
        question: "What does 'patawan' mean in Huttese?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'boonta eve classic',
        question: "Translate 'boonta eve classic' into Basic (Galactic Basic Standard).",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'yoka',
        options: ['yoka', 'yoda', 'yoyo', 'yukka'],
        question: "What does 'yoka' mean in Huttese?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'goola',
        options: ['goola', 'gruta', 'gusta', 'gappa'],
        question: "Which word means 'big' in Huttese?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'wonga',
        question: "Translate 'wonga' into Basic (Galactic Basic Standard).",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '00a1cf07-da24-4946-a8e2-9da2098297c8',
    title: "Discover Klingon: Beginner's Vocabulary Expedition!",
    description:
      "Welcome to the world of Klingon! This quiz is your gateway to learning the basics of the fearsome Klingon language. Whether you're a Star Trek enthusiast or just curious about extraterrestrial tongues, this beginner's vocabulary expedition will introduce you to essential words and phrases in Klingon. Qapla'!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'Klingon',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'tlhIngan Hol',
        options: ['klingonese', 'Klingese', 'tlhIngan Hol', 'klingu'],
        question: 'What is the Klingon word for the Klingon language?',
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: "ghobe'",
        options: ["ghobe'", "vIghobe'", "qo'noS", 'quv'],
        question: "Translate 'enemy' into Klingon.",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: "Heghlu'meH QaQ jajvam",
        question: "What is the Klingon phrase that means 'Today is a good day to die'?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'petaQ',
        options: ['petaQ', "bat'leth", 'Duj', "qo'"],
        question: 'Which word is a Klingon insult?',
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: "Qapla'",
        options: ["Qapla'", 'Duj', 'petaQ', "Qo'noS"],
        question: 'What is the traditional Klingon wish for success?',
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'a8e28588-c025-44ba-a5d0-f136b67298c8',
    title: 'Conquer Klingon: Intermediate Vocabulary Challenge!',
    description:
      "Step up your game with the Conquer Klingon intermediate vocabulary challenge! This quiz will test your knowledge of Klingon words and phrases, from the serious to the absurd. Whether you're a dedicated Star Trek fan or a linguistics enthusiast, this challenge will help you deepen your understanding of the warrior's tongue. Qapla'!",
    difficulty: 'intermediate',
    language: 'Klingon',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: "Qo'noS",
        options: ["Qo'noS", 'Kronos', 'QeyliS', 'Koroth'],
        question: 'What is the Klingon homeworld called?',
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'toH',
        options: ['toH', 'jajvam', 'batlh', 'Hegh'],
        question: "Which word means 'So!' or 'Well!' in Klingon?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'maHegh',
        question: "How do you say 'We die' in Klingon?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: "nuqDaq 'oH puchpa''e'",
        question: "Translate the following into Klingon: 'Where is the bathroom?'",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'nagh',
        options: ['taj', 'nagh', 'Hoch', "Qo'"],
        question: "What is the Klingon word for 'rock'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'aa340aeb-db29-4a51-815f-f0983e11ff17',
    title: "Discover French: Beginner's Vocabulary Adventure!",
    description:
      "Bienvenue! Dive into the beautiful French language with this beginner's vocabulary adventure. From everyday words to some fun and quirky terms, this quiz is designed to inspire and challenge you. Whether you're planning a trip to France or just love languages, this quiz will help you get started on your French learning journey. Bon courage!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'French',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'chien',
        options: ['chat', 'chien', 'oiseau', 'poisson'],
        question: "What is the French word for 'dog'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'fromage',
        options: ['pain', 'lait', 'fromage', 'vin'],
        question: "Which word means 'cheese' in French?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'bonjour',
        question: "How do you say 'hello' in French?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'quatre',
        options: ['trois', 'quatre', 'cinq', 'six'],
        question: "What is the French word for 'four'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'escargot',
        options: ['pâté', 'baguette', 'escargot', 'croissant'],
        question: 'Which word refers to snails as a dish in French cuisine?',
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'f92b15e9-0544-4e6f-9dab-92dc26e952ac',
    title: 'Master French: Intermediate Vocabulary Quest!',
    description:
      "Bienvenue to the Master French Vocabulary Quest! This quiz is designed for those who have a grasp of the basics and are ready to tackle more intermediate French words and phrases. From the practical to the whimsical, this quiz will challenge your knowledge and inspire you to learn more. Let's embark on this linguistic adventure together!",
    difficulty: 'intermediate',
    language: 'French',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'bibliothèque',
        options: ['librairie', 'bibliothèque', 'école', 'mairie'],
        question: "What is the French word for 'library'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'éclair',
        options: ['tarte', 'éclair', 'gâteau', 'crêpe'],
        question: "Which French pastry translates to 'lightning'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'le nez',
        question: "What is the French word for 'the nose'?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'le ciel est bleu',
        question: "Translate the sentence 'The sky is blue' into French.",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'moulin',
        options: ['château', 'pont', 'moulin', 'église'],
        question: "Which word means 'mill' in French?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'a2f6fbb5-4a7d-4891-8d00-54e9a85fc217',
    title: 'Conquer French: Advanced Vocabulary Challenge!',
    description:
      'Bienvenue to the Conquer French Advanced Vocabulary Challenge! This quiz is designed for those who have mastered the basics and are ready to dive into the more complex and nuanced aspects of the French language. From serious linguistic inquiries to some delightfully absurd ones, this quiz will test your advanced French vocabulary. Are you ready to prove your prowess? Bonne chance!',
    difficulty: 'advanced',
    language: 'French',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'anticonstitutionnellement',
        options: [
          'anticonstitutionnellement',
          'incompréhensiblement',
          'indubitablement',
          'philanthropiquement',
        ],
        question:
          "What is the longest word in the French language, meaning 'in an unconstitutional manner'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'pamplemousse',
        options: ['citron', 'orange', 'pamplemousse', 'ananas'],
        question: "Which French word for a fruit translates humorously to 'grapefruit'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'le ver vert va vers le verre vert',
        question:
          "Translate the tongue twister 'The green worm goes towards the green glass' into French.",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'trou noir',
        options: ['trou noir', 'étoile filante', 'galaxie', 'planète'],
        question: "What is the French term for 'black hole'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'évanouissement',
        question: "What is the French word for 'fainting'?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '7082918b-25a5-4057-a85f-5689ef35c388',
    title: 'Unlock Arabic: Fun and Challenging Vocabulary Quiz!',
    description:
      'Dive into the rich and captivating world of Arabic with this engaging quiz! Designed to inspire and challenge, this quiz covers a range of vocabulary from serious to absurd. Test your knowledge and learn new words that will enhance your understanding of this beautiful language. Are you ready for the challenge?',
    difficulty: 'intermediate',
    language: 'Arabic',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'كتاب',
        options: ['بيت', 'سيارة', 'كتاب', 'شجرة'],
        question: "What is the Arabic word for 'book'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'شمس',
        options: ['قمر', 'نجم', 'شمس', 'سماء'],
        question: "Which word means 'sun' in Arabic?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'تفاحة',
        question: "What is the Arabic word for 'apple'?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'سيارة حمراء',
        question: "Translate the phrase 'red car' into Arabic.",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'أرنبة',
        options: ['قطة', 'كلب', 'أرنبة', 'بقرة'],
        question: "Which Arabic word translates to 'rabbit'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '424db81c-07cd-4bc3-bfc2-74892524dadf',
    title: "Embark on an Arabic Adventure: Beginner's Vocabulary Exploration!",
    description:
      "Welcome to your Arabic adventure! This beginner's vocabulary exploration will take you on a journey through the basics of the Arabic language. From everyday words to some fun and quirky terms, this quiz is designed to inspire and encourage you as you begin your Arabic learning journey. Let's get started!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'Arabic',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'كتاب',
        options: ['كتاب', 'سيارة', 'شجرة', 'مدينة'],
        question: "What is the Arabic word for 'book'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'شمس',
        options: ['بحر', 'شمس', 'قمر', 'سماء'],
        question: "Which word means 'sun' in Arabic?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'تفاحة',
        question: "What is the Arabic word for 'apple'?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'بيت أبيض',
        question: "Translate the phrase 'White House' into Arabic.",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'قطة',
        options: ['كلب', 'فأر', 'قطة', 'طائر'],
        question: "Which Arabic word translates to 'cat'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '6af21129-6a39-4b58-9a34-fa7a1d596b2e',
    title: 'Master Arabic: Advanced Vocabulary Odyssey!',
    description:
      'Prepare to embark on an epic journey through the advanced levels of Arabic vocabulary! From serious linguistic inquiries to some delightfully absurd ones, this quiz will test your knowledge and expand your understanding of the Arabic language. Are you ready to prove your mastery?',
    difficulty: 'advanced',
    language: 'Arabic',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'النفاق',
        options: ['النفاق', 'الحب', 'السعادة', 'السلام'],
        question: "What is the Arabic word for 'hypocrisy'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'ملعقة',
        options: ['ملعقة', 'سكين', 'شوكة', 'طبق'],
        question: "Which Arabic word translates to 'spoon'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'العزيز',
        question: "Translate the Arabic word 'Al-Aziz' into English.",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'جملة بنية سببية',
        question: "What is the term in Arabic grammar for 'causal sentence'?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'خروف طائر',
        options: ['خروف طائر', 'سمك طائر', 'قطة طائرة', 'حصان طائر'],
        question:
          "What would be an absurd literal translation of the term 'flying sheep' into Arabic?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'f3f61208-aa37-458b-808d-d65c99344a01',
    title: 'Unleash Your Danish Mastery: Advanced Vocabulary Extravaganza!',
    description:
      'Get ready to unleash your Danish mastery with this advanced vocabulary extravaganza! From serious linguistic inquiries to some hilariously absurd ones, this quiz will push your knowledge of Danish to the limit. Are you prepared to tackle the challenges and expand your Danish vocabulary?',
    difficulty: 'advanced',
    language: 'Danish',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'skæbne',
        options: ['lykke', 'kærlighed', 'skæbne', 'fred'],
        question: "What is the Danish word for 'fate'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'æblekage',
        options: ['kartoffelmos', 'frikadeller', 'æblekage', 'rødbeder'],
        question: "Which Danish dish translates to 'apple cake'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'jeg elsker dig',
        question: "Translate the phrase 'I love you' into Danish.",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'tusindfryd',
        question: "What is the Danish word for 'daisy'?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'flyvende grise',
        options: ['flyvende grise', 'svømmende katte', 'gående fisk', 'løbende hunde'],
        question:
          "What would be an absurd literal translation of the term 'flying pigs' into Danish?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: '1e81eb49-4b55-44fe-9009-cfd45be1201e',
    title: "Discover Danish: Beginner's Vocabulary Quest!",
    description:
      "Embark on a thrilling journey to discover the Danish language with this beginner's vocabulary quest! Whether you're just starting out or brushing up on your basics, this quiz will introduce you to essential Danish words and phrases. Get ready to explore the beauty of Danish language and culture!",
    difficulty: 'beginner',
    language: 'Danish',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'hund',
        options: ['kat', 'hund', 'fisk', 'fugl'],
        question: "What is the Danish word for 'dog'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'tak',
        options: ['ja', 'nej', 'hej', 'tak'],
        question: "Which Danish word means 'thank you'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'rød',
        question: "What is the Danish word for 'red'?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'godmorgen',
        question: "How do you say 'good morning' in Danish?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'flyvende elefanter',
        options: ['flyvende elefanter', 'svømmende hunde', 'hoppende giraffer', 'løbende katte'],
        question:
          "What would be an absurd literal translation of the term 'flying elephants' into Danish?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 'e5b2f632-f65f-4b56-9a9a-bcc1c1323725',
    title: 'Explore Danish: Intermediate Vocabulary Adventure!',
    description:
      'Embark on an exciting journey through intermediate Danish vocabulary with this engaging quiz! From serious linguistic inquiries to some delightfully absurd ones, this quiz will challenge and expand your knowledge of the Danish language. Are you ready for the adventure?',
    difficulty: 'intermediate',
    language: 'Danish',
    questions: [
      {
        correct_answer: 'hus',
        options: ['bil', 'bog', 'hus', 'træ'],
        question: "What is the Danish word for 'house'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'solnedgang',
        options: ['regnvejr', 'sne', 'solnedgang', 'torden'],
        question: "Which Danish word translates to 'sunset'?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'vandmelon',
        question: "What is the Danish word for 'watermelon'?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'godnat',
        question: "How do you say 'goodnight' in Danish?",
        type: 'free_text',
      },
      {
        correct_answer: 'flyvende hvaler',
        options: ['flyvende hvaler', 'svømmende bjørne', 'hoppende pingviner', 'løbende sæler'],
        question:
          "What would be an absurd literal translation of the term 'flying whales' into Danish?",
        type: 'single_choice',
      },
    ],
  },
];
